{
    "id": "3c687b608c224c9c816c8de5525affd0",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Follow the directions ……………………… or this medicine may be harmful.",
            "description": "Carefully is an adverb. We use an adverb to modify verbs. Here it modifies the verb follow. ",
            "answers": [
                "care",
                "careful",
                "carefully"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "One has to be ……………………. to work as a lumberjack.",
            "description": "Hardy mean strong or able-bodied.",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardy",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "After that ……………………….. experience I shook for a week.",
            "description": "The present participle is used to talk about the people or things that cause those feelings. ",
            "answers": [
                "harrowing",
                "harrowed"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The harsh light ………………………. my eyes.",
            "description": "Hurt is the present and past simple form of hurt. ",
            "answers": [
                "hurt",
                "hurted"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There wasn’t much time so I dressed ………………………",
            "description": "Hastily means quickly.",
            "answers": [
                "haste",
                "hastily",
                "hastely"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A ……………………… search turned up the missing earring.",
            "description": "Hasty is an adjective hastily is an adverb. We need an adjective here. ",
            "answers": [
                "haste",
                "hasty",
                "hastily"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She isn’t ………………………. to be a good dancer.",
            "description": "Enough goes after the adjective modified by it. ",
            "answers": [
                "enough graceful",
                "graceful enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The queen received her subjects in a ……………………….. manner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "grand",
                "grant"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He knew ……………………….. well what I was trying to say.",
            "description": "Full can also be used as an adverb. ",
            "answers": [
                "full",
                "fully",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The expedition was ………………………….. with danger.",
            "description": "Fraught with means filled with.",
            "answers": [
                "fought",
                "fraught",
                "wrought"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He speaks too ………………….. to be heard.",
            "description": "We need the adverb softly to modify the verb speaks. ",
            "answers": [
                "soft",
                "softly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ……………………. a case of mistaken identity.",
            "description": "Solely means purely. ",
            "answers": [
                "sole",
                "solely",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}